{"steps":[{"value":1000000,"stringValue":"1,000,000","index":15,"isSafe":true},{"value":500000,"stringValue":"500,000","index":14,"isSafe":false},{"value":250000,"stringValue":"250,000","index":13,"isSafe":false},{"value":125000,"stringValue":"125,000","index":12,"isSafe":false},{"value":64000,"stringValue":"64,000","index":11,"isSafe":false},{"value":32000,"stringValue":"32,000","index":10,"isSafe":true},{"value":16000,"stringValue":"16,000","index":9,"isSafe":false},{"value":8000,"stringValue":"8,000","index":8,"isSafe":false},{"value":4000,"stringValue":"4,000","index":7,"isSafe":false},{"value":2000,"stringValue":"2,000","index":6,"isSafe":false},{"value":1000,"stringValue":"1,000","index":5,"isSafe":true},{"value":500,"stringValue":"500","index":4,"isSafe":false},{"value":300,"stringValue":"300","index":3,"isSafe":false},{"value":200,"stringValue":"200","index":2,"isSafe":false},{"value":100,"stringValue":"100","index":1,"isSafe":false}],"games":[[{"Amount":"$100","Question":"Finish the saying: Live, Laugh and what?","A":"Bacon","B":"Love","C":"Laundry","D":"Wine","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$200","Question":"What animal is Disney's Dumbo?","A":"Deer","B":"Fish","C":"Elephant","D":"Bear","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$300","Question":"The show The Queens's Gambit is about an orphan who makes her way in the world by doing what?","A":"Marrying a prince","B":"Playing Chess","C":"Playing Bridge","D":"Impersonating Queen Liz","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$500","Question":"In National Treasure the ragtag gang of treasure seekers finds their map on the back of what important document?","A":"The Constitution","B":"The Emancipation Proclamation","C":"The Declaration of Independence","D":"The Silence Dogood Letters","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$1,000","Question":"Which of the following types of pasta is not commonly stuffed with a filling?","A":"Tortellini","B":"Ravioli","C":"Cannelloni","D":"Gnocchi","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$2,000","Question":"In order to complete the 2019-2020 NBA season the league created a bubble in what city?","A":"Los Angeles","B":"Houston","C":"Orlando","D":"Miami","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$4,000","Question":"What country is Paddington Bear originally from?","A":"Scotland","B":"Peru","C":"Bolivia","D":"Zimbabwe","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$8,000","Question":"Post-Impressionist Paul Gaugin contracted syphillis and died in what Pacific nation?","A":"Thailand","B":"Bali","C":"Indonesia","D":"Tahiti","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$16,000","Question":"Rapper Tyler, The Creator is a founding member of what rap crew?","A":"Camp Flog","B":"Bad Boys","C":"Odd Future","D":"Migos","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$32,000","Question":"In 2020 The Pulitzer Prize awarded its very first audio reporting award to what podcast?","A":"This American Life","B":"Radiolab","C":"All Things Considered","D":"The Daily","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$64,000","Question":"What Caribbean nation has a Trident on its flag?","A":"Grenada","B":"Barbados","C":"Saint Lucia","D":"Bahamas","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$125,000","Question":"What are the two planets in our solar system that do not have any moons?","A":"Neptune & Pluto","B":"Mercury & Pluto","C":"Venus & Neptune","D":"Mercury & Venus","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$250,000","Question":"In 2009, Barack Obama won the Nobel Peace Prize, the first sitting U.S. president to do so since whom?","A":"Woodrow Wilson","B":"Jimmy Carter","C":"Franklin Roosevelt","D":"Lyndon Johnson","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$500,000","Question":"How many strings does a harp have?","A":"30","B":"41","C":"47","D":"52","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$1,000,000","Question":"Besides Roma, what other foreign-language film was nominated for 10 Academy Awards?","A":"A Separation","B":"Franny & Alexander","C":"Parasite","D":"Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon","Answer":"D"}],[{"Amount":"$100","Question":"How many boroughs are there in New York City?","A":"4","B":"5","C":"6","D":"3","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$200","Question":"Cardi B & Megan Thee Stallion's smash hit WAP scared men because it was about what?","A":"Women empowering women to enjoy sex","B":"Women acknowleding they enjoy sex","C":"Wet Ass Pussies","D":"All of the above","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$300","Question":"What is the name of the app where you can easily waste 2 hours watching teenage kids do silly dances, dogs doing silly things, and whatever weird shit your algorithim spits out?","A":"Apple Stocks","B":"Periscope","C":"TikTok","D":"Vine","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$500","Question":"Baby Yoda will always be Baby Yoda to me and The Child to Mando, even though his name was revealed to be what?","A":"Rupert","B":"Yoda Jr.","C":"Grogu","D":"Snafu","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$1,000","Question":"On what island is the state capital Honolulu located?","A":"Oahu","B":"Hawai'i","C":"Maui","D":"Lanai","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$2,000","Question":"In high school biology you learned about breeding genotypes using what kind of diagram?","A":"Taxonomy Chart","B":"Punnett Square","C":"Venn Diagram","D":"Segmentation Chart","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$4,000","Question":"Remember Wild Wild Country? What is the name for the people in the cult?","A":"Sheelas","B":"Moonies","C":"Oshos","D":"Rajneeshees","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$8,000","Question":"The 2020 Olympics have been postponed, but the rest are still on schedule. Where are the 2024 games set to be held?","A":"Beijing","B":"Los Angeles","C":"Madrid","D":"Paris","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$16,000","Question":"Shall I compare thee to a summer’s day? is the opening line to what type of poem written by Shakespeare?","A":"Sonnet","B":"Ode","C":"Epic","D":"Pastoral","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$32,000","Question":"In backgammon, what is is called when you take pieces off the board?","A":"Removing checkers","B":"Doubling Away","C":"Bearing Off","D":"Gammoning","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$64,000","Question":"On D-Day the five beaches stormed at Normandy were codenamed Utah, Omaha, Sword, Gold and what?","A":"Wyoming","B":"Silver","C":"Juno","D":"Yellow","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$125,000","Question":"The opening images to Kubrick's 2001: A Space Odyssey are accompanied by the classical piece Also sprach Zarathustra, which was composed by whom?","A":"Beethoven","B":"Wagner","C":"Schönberg","D":"Strauss","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$250,000","Question":"Victoria Falls is located at the border of which two countries?","A":"Zimbabwe & Mozambique","B":"Zimbabwe & Zambia","C":"Zimbabwe & Botswana","D":"Zimbabwe & South Africa","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$500,000","Question":"Including successful & botched flights how mant space missions were launched as part of the Apollo program?","A":"32","B":"16","C":"35","D":"45","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$1,000,000","Question":"Of all the famous swashbucklers, which pirate is given credit for creating the original version of the Jolly Roger?","A":"Blackbeard","B":"Redbeard","C":"Captain Kidd","D":"Calico Jack","Answer":"D"}],[{"Amount":"$100","Question":"A sweater that covers your neck is called a what?","A":"Cowl neck","B":"Turtleneck","C":"Hoodie","D":"Boatneck","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$200","Question":"What is the name of the legendary disco nightclub of 1970s NYC?","A":"Studio 54","B":"Studio 2","C":"Studio H","D":"Studio Blue22","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$300","Question":"The start of the Trojan War is attributed to the theft of what lady?","A":"Karen","B":"Susan","C":"Cassandra","D":"Helen","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$500","Question":"A martini is made dirty by the addition of what garnish?","A":"Lemon Peel","B":"Olives","C":"Fun-sized onions","D":"Orange Wedge","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$1,000","Question":"Whch one of these films is NOT a teen remake of a Shakespeare play?","A":"She's All That","B":"10 Things I Hate About You","C":"O","D":"She's The Man","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$2,000","Question":"Gilllian Anderson served Tory despicableness on the latest season of The Crown, if Netflix were to do a prequel series that would show Maggie working as a what?","A":"Shopkeeper","B":"Research Chemist","C":"The Actual Devil","D":"Pharmacist","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$4,000","Question":"El Conejo Malo is the translated name of what reggaeton superstar?","A":"Bad Bunny","B":"J Balvin","C":"Daddy Yankee","D":"Ozuna","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$8,000","Question":"The first ever world cup was held in Uruguay in 1039, what team took home the trophy?","A":"Brazil","B":"England","C":"Uruguay","D":"Germany","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$16,000","Question":"Marcel Duchamp’s famous urinal is actually named what?","A":"Toilet","B":"Fountain","C":"Grinder","D":"Sink","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$32,000","Question":"In the LCD Soundsystem song, Losing My Edge, James Murphy was there for all the following things except which?","A":"when John Cage played 4 minutes and 53 seconds of silence in 1952","B":"at the Paradise Garage DJ booth with Larry Levan.","C":"when Captain Beefheart started up his first band","D":"waking up naked on the beach in Ibiza in 1988","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$64,000","Question":"Which one of the following is not a section of elements on the periodic table?","A":"Metals","B":"Non Metals","C":"Metalloids","D":"Gases","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$125,000","Question":"Who is the only musician to be inducted to the Rock & Roll Hall of Fame a record three times?","A":"Eric Clapton","B":"Paul McCartney","C":"Paul Simon","D":"Neil Young","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$250,000","Question":"In an IronMan Triathlon, how long is the biking portion of this asinine event?","A":"50 miles","B":"112 miles","C":"67 miles","D":"150 miles","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$500,000","Question":"In what year was construction on the Berlin Wall started?","A":"1946","B":"1961","C":"1956","D":"1950","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$1,000,000","Question":"The HBO miniseries Band of Brothers chronicles 101st Airborne Division and is a pretty serious show. So it was all the more weird when this funny man made a cameo on the battlefield.","A":"Jimmy Fallon","B":"Bill Murray","C":"Jason Biggs","D":"Ashton Kutcher","Answer":"A"}],[{"Amount":"$100","Question":"In the song Seven Days by Craig David, what are he and his date doing on Sunday?","A":"Just meeting","B":"Making love","C":"Going for a drink","D":"Chilling","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$200","Question":"Which of the following is not an iconic piece of IKEA furniture?","A":"BILLY","B":"RIBBA","C":"MALM","D":"MIDSOMMAR","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$300","Question":"In the Fast and the Furious franchise, Dominic Toretto says he lives his life how?","A":"Collecting pinks","B":"With his familia","C":"Drinking coronas","D":"A 1/4 mile at a time","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$500","Question":"In his Oscar-winning song Lose Yourself, what is the vomit on Eminem’s sweater comprised of?","A":"Mom's Detroit Style Pizza","B":"Mom's Hotpockets","C":"Mom's Spaghetti","D":"Mom's Mac & Cheese","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$1,000","Question":"Philip Pullman is probably most well known for his novel The Golden Compass. However this book is actually the first in a triology of works called what?","A":"Chronicles of Narnia","B":"His Dark Materials","C":"Space Ghosts vs God","D":"Galaxy Quest","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$2,000","Question":"To go hard in the paint is a saying that originates from what sport?","A":"Hockey","B":"Football","C":"Basketball","D":"Cheerleading","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$4,000","Question":"Jazz musician Thelonius Monk is most well known for being a virtuoso at what instrument?","A":"Drums","B":"Saxophone","C":"Clarinet","D":"Piano","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$8,000","Question":"Manchego is a cheese produced from the milk of what animal?","A":"Cow","B":"Buffalo","C":"Sheep","D":"Goat","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$16,000","Question":"Who played the 11th version of The Doctor on Doctor Who?","A":"Matt Smith","B":"David Tennant","C":"Jodie Whittaker","D":"Peter Capaldi","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$32,000","Question":"Gin is really just vodka with interesting flavors called botanicals. What is the most common gin botanical?","A":"Coriander","B":"Pine","C":"Fennel","D":"Juniper","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$64,000","Question":"Fan fiction is a world unto itself - which of the following terms is not a classification for a fanfic story?","A":"Ship","B":"Drabble","C":"Pendom","D":"Ficlet","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$125,000","Question":"In curling, teams alternate trying to score points in rounds of play that are called what?","A":"Downs","B":"Goals","C":"Ends","D":"Tries","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$250,000","Question":"What was the name of the dictator that is recognized for ruling over Yugoslavia in the post-World War II period?","A":"Josip Tito","B":"Nicolae Ceaușescu","C":"Slobodan Milošević","D":"Mátyás Rákosi","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$500,000","Question":"Each of the following Shakespeare plays includes the deaths of more than 5 characters except which one?","A":"Romeo & Juliet","B":"Othello","C":"King Lear","D":"Julius Caesar","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$1,000,000","Question":"In music theory, the cirlce of fifths is used to do what?","A":"Idenitfy tempo","B":"Illustrate key signatures","C":"Organize chromatic pitches","D":"Calculate diatonics","Answer":"C"}],[{"Amount":"$100","Question":"Finish this famous movie line: Yippee Ki Yay...","A":"It's Christmas!","B":"Motherfucker!","C":"Butthead!","D":"KA-POW!","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$200","Question":"Maps of the earth are divided into what two kinds of lines?","A":"Longitude & Latitude","B":"Latitude & Fatitude","C":"Prime Meridians & Equators","D":"Long and Short","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$300","Question":"Grave Digger, Sin City Hustler and Towasaurus Wrex are names of what?","A":"Wrestlers","B":"College Football Players","C":"Monster Trucks","D":"Nicknames of some douchebag's collegues at a wealth management firm","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$500","Question":"Airports are commonly divided into buildings known as what?","A":"Houses","B":"Hangars","C":"Terminals","D":"Palaces","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$1,000","Question":"In World War II the Axis powers were Germany, Japan and what other nation?","A":"Soviet Union","B":"Spain","C":"Italy","D":"Hungary","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$2,000","Question":"Bulgogi beef is a delicious style of meat that comes from what country?","A":"Korea","B":"Japan","C":"China","D":"Thailand","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$4,000","Question":"According to the iconic movie dad Mel Horowitz, everywhere in LA takes how long to get to?","A":"60 minutes","B":"45 minutes","C":"20 minutes","D":"90 minutes","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$8,000","Question":"Midcentury furniture aficionados will most closely aligh Eames with the design of what type of furniture?","A":"Chair","B":"Dresser","C":"Toilet","D":"Coffee Table","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$16,000","Question":"Buzz Aldrin and Neil Armstrong walked on the moon, but what was the name of the dude that stayed in the ship?","A":"Allan Shepard","B":"Michael Collins","C":"Gus Grissom","D":"Jim Lovell","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$32,000","Question":"Tiki drinks are trpoical-style concoctions inspired by the flavors and cultures of Polynesia. The first ever tiki bar in the United States was in which city?","A":"Miami","B":"Los Angeles","C":"Honolulu","D":"Las Vegas","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$64,000","Question":"Which of the following religius observances lasts for the shortest period of time?","A":"Ramadan","B":"Lent","C":"Kwanzaa","D":"Diwali","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$125,000","Question":"Accroding to the World Wildlife Foundation, 16 species as listed as Critically Endangered, what two animals make up half of the list, contibuting 3 species each?","A":"Gorilla & Rhino","B":"Rhino & Elephant","C":"Tiger & Orangutan","D":"Tiger & Gorilla","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$250,000","Question":"The Burj Khalifa is the world's tallest building, but prior to it's completion, which skyscraper held the title?","A":"The Shanghai Tower","B":"The Petronas Towers","C":"Sears Tower","D":"Taipei 101","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$500,000","Question":"Singultus is medical name for what condition?","A":"Stomach growls","B":"Migraines","C":"Clogged ear canal","D":"Hiccups","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$1,000,000","Question":"The United Nations is presided over by the Secretary-General, who can serve up to two terms, how long is the allowable term?","A":"8 Years","B":"6 Years","C":"10 Years","D":"14 Years","Answer":"C"}],[{"Amount":"$100","Question":"What is the name of the President's plane?","A":"Air Force One","B":"The Concorde","C":"Budgie the Little Helicopter","D":"ConAir","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$200","Question":"What is Superman allergic to?","A":"Pollen","B":"Tree nuts","C":"Kryptonite","D":"Cats","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$300","Question":"According to the opening number, The Phantom of the Opera is... where?","A":"The Opera House","B":"The Light Booth","C":"Inside Your Mind","D":"Hell","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$500","Question":"Which one of these brands has not gained popularity due to podcast advertising?","A":"Casper","B":"McDonalds","C":"Squarespace","D":"Zip Recruiter","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$1,000","Question":"I could never be friends with someone who willingly signed up to run a trail race combined with obstacles popularly known as what?","A":"Triathalons","B":"Tough Mudders","C":"Fun Runs","D":"Dirt Jams","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$2,000","Question":"What Zodiac sign encompasses the dates September 23 - October 22?","A":"Gemini","B":"Sagittarius","C":"Leo","D":"Libra","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$4,000","Question":"Vinyl records are engineered to rotate at three speeds, 33 bpm, 45 bpm and what?","A":"78bpm","B":"85bpm","C":"20bpm","D":"96bpm","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$8,000","Question":"Cognac is a spirit distilled from what product?","A":"Wheat","B":"Sugar","C":"Grapes","D":"Apples","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$16,000","Question":"Charles Ingram cheated on the UK version of Who Wants To Be A Millionaire in 2001. What rank did he hold in the British Army?","A":"Private","B":"Captain","C":"Major","D":"Lieutenant","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$32,000","Question":"In Formula 1, Ferrari are the leaders with over 200 race wins. What team follows in the number two spot with 182 race wins?","A":"Mercedes","B":"Williams","C":"McLaren","D":"Red Bull","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$64,000","Question":"Which of the following is not the name of a Bond girl?","A":"Christmas Jones","B":"Felicity Ryder","C":"Holly Goodhead","D":"Kissy Suzuki","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$125,000","Question":"The reservoir in Central Park is named after who?","A":"John F. Kennedy","B":"Ed Koch","C":"Frederick Law Olmsted","D":"Jaquie Kennedy Onassis","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$250,000","Question":"The pride flag that features yellow, white, purple and black horizontral stripes is for what part of the LBGTQIA+ community?","A":"Nonbinary","B":"Pansexual","C":"Asexual","D":"Bisexual","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$500,000","Question":"Which of the following firms was bought out by JPMorgan Chase during the 2008 recession?","A":"Lehman Brothers","B":"Merrill Lynch","C":"Bear Stearns","D":"Goldman Sachs","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$1,000,000","Question":"Of the 63 designated US National Parks, how many are in Alaska?","A":"10","B":"5","C":"12","D":"8","Answer":"D"}],[{"Amount":"$100","Question":"Where does the Daytona 500 take place?","A":"Daytona, FL","B":"Orlando, FL","C":"Indianapolis, IN","D":"Houston, TX","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$200","Question":"CB2 is the sister brand for what other home goods brand?","A":"West Elm","B":"IKEA","C":"Crate & Barrel","D":"HomeGoods","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$300","Question":"What is Kel Kimbel's beverage of choice?","A":"Orange Soda","B":"Faygo","C":"Lipton Tea","D":"Cold milk","Answer":"A"},{"Amount":"$500","Question":"TikTok user 420doggface208 went viral this year for skateboarding and doing what?","A":"Taking Names","B":"Smoking a fat one","C":"Drinking cranberry juice","D":"Parkour","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$1,000","Question":"During the original airing of the Sopranos, which structure was removed from the opening titles sequece?","A":"Brooklyn Bridge","B":"George Washington Bridge","C":"Giants Stadium","D":"The World Trade Center","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$2,000","Question":"Prior to the 19-century, in England, in order of a town to be upgraded to a city designation, it was required to have what feature?","A":"A funeral home","B":"A newspaper","C":"A cathedral","D":"A jail","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$4,000","Question":"Diabetes develops as a result of a problem in which organ?","A":"Colon","B":"Kidney","C":"Liver","D":"Pancreas","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$8,000","Question":"In S.E.Hinton's The Outsiders the two rival gangs are called what?","A":"The Jets & The Sharks","B":"The Greasers & The Socials","C":"The Greasers & The Thunderbirds","D":"The Scorpions & The Thunderbirds","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$16,000","Question":"The Lollapalooza music festival in Chicago was founded by the frontman of what alternative '90s band?","A":"Stone Temple Pilots","B":"Jane's Addiction","C":"Crash Test Dummies","D":"Third Eye Blind","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$32,000","Question":"In Gulliver’s Travels, Gulliver travels to four islands, upon his arrival on the last island, he is greeted by horse-like creatures known as what?","A":"Lilliputs","B":"Yahoos","C":"Houyhnhnms","D":"Brobdingnags","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$64,000","Question":"With awardees including Renzo Piano and Oscar Niemeyer the Pritzker Award is given to accomplished individuals in what discipline?","A":"Dance","B":"Engineering","C":"Architecture","D":"Classical Music","Answer":"C"},{"Amount":"$125,000","Question":"Like humans, plants have vascular systems - what are the names of the two types of tubes found inside plants?","A":"Brachial & Basilic","B":"Axillaries & Thelia","C":"Fauces & Thyloids","D":"Xylem & Phoelm","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$250,000","Question":"In a game of Mahjong each player is allotted how many tiles at the start of the game?","A":"7","B":"10","C":"12","D":"13","Answer":"D"},{"Amount":"$500,000","Question":"Meryl Streep might be the queen of the Academy Awards with a total of 21 nominations, but which Actor has the most nominations across the acting categories?","A":"Leonardo DiCaprio","B":"Jack Nicholson","C":"Laurence Olivier","D":"Paul Newman","Answer":"B"},{"Amount":"$1,000,000","Question":"A strait is defined as a narrow body of water that connects two larger bodies of water. What is the longest strait coming in at over 900km?","A":"Strait of Malacca","B":"Bering Strait","C":"Strait of Magellan","D":"Formossa Strait","Answer":"A"}]],"ff":[{"Question":"Put these Canadian Territories in order from East to West.","A":"Manitoba","B":"Ontario","C":"Nova Scotia","D":"Yukon","Answer":"C, B, A, D"},{"Question":"Put the Harry Potter books in order of release date.","A":"Chamber of Secrets","B":"Half-Blood Prince","C":"Goblet of Fire","D":"Prisoner of Azkaban","Answer":"A, D, C, B"},{"Question":"Put the following cities in order of population size from smallest to biggest.","A":"Chicago","B":"Houston","C":"Los Angeles","D":"Philadelphia","Answer":"D, B, A, C"},{"Question":"Put these Nintendo systems in order of their release.","A":"GameBoy Color","B":"Wii","C":"Gamecube","D":"DS","Answer":"A, C, D, B"},{"Question":"Put these paper sizes in order for biggest to smallest.","A":"Letter","B":"A4","C":"Tabloid","D":"Legal","Answer":"C, D, B, A"},{"Question":"Put the Indiana Jones movies in release order.","A":"Crystal Skull","B":"Temple of Doom","C":"Raiders of the Lost Ark","D":"Last Crusade","Answer":"C, B, D, A"},{"Question":"Put these measurements in order from biggest to smallest volume.","A":"Pint","B":"Milliliter","C":"Gallon","D":"Liter","Answer":"C, D, A, B"}]}
